Come on , the bus won 't wait .
Hurry , come on .
Hurry . Get on the bus . The weather 's turning .
Come on .
Up you get .
Wait ! Wait for me !
Stop !
Wait !
Come back here !
Hello ?
Is anyone home ?
I 'm a foreigner and I 'm lost !
I know someone 's there . Please !
Well , this is quite a revelation to me , Professor .
I mean , I had no idea an expert on insects
could provide the police with such invaluable help
in a homicide investigation .
Normally we don 't , but I made the unfortunate error
of becoming an expert on cadaveric fauna .
You see , Kurt ...
John , weâ   re not going through that whole number again , are we ?
Yes , we are , just like we did the first time
you came here all those years ago .
Do you remember , Rudy , the first case we solved together ?
When a dead body is exposed to the elements ,
sooner or later it 's eaten up by insects .
Hey !
You naughty girl .
Hey ! Where did you get this ?
You know you could cut yourself ?
Look . Look here . You could cut yourself with this .
See . It 's not a toy .
Not a toy . Where did you find it ?
Oh . Outside .
And who , may I ask , put it out there ?
I donâ   t want you ever ... I don 't want you ever , ever ,
Ook , ook !
Oh , I forgot to introduce you . This is Inga .
She 's my nurse .
If I pick out something with my laser , she never forgets it .
She 's also my friend too , aren 't you , Inga ?
But she 's a very good nurse .
Insects that eat cadavers are divided into eight groups .
Eight groups of insects that follow one another ,
installing themselves at exact moments
and on precise terms .
Never sooner and never later .
We call them the eight squadrons of death .
First comes the common fly .
Lays its eggs in the rotting corpse .
And thus the cycle begins .
Each group stays 15 days .
15 ! You multiply it by 8 .
- The number of the groups is ... - Four months .
In the case of this head
the cycle not only seems to be complete
but to have been repeated .
- Which puts us at ... - Eight months .
Now I see .
By calculating the presence and the growth
of the flies or the maggots ,
you can pinpoint the exact date of death .
Or murder .
So , our victim was decapitated some eight months ago .
And 15 days . Aren 't you forgetting something ?
15 days while the body was submerged in the lake ,
before the putrefying gasses brought it to the surface ,
and thence to the shore , where the first flies arrived .
Eight and a half months , then .
Perhaps a little less .
The mountain wind , the FÃ ¶ hn , was unusually warm this year .
So , we could say that she lost her head
somewhere between September 7th and 10th .
Am I right , John ? Let 's see now , about that time .
The first girl to disappear , that was September 9th .
A 14-year-old Danish tourist named Vera Brandt .
- The body was never found . - Just like the other girl 's .
Like Greta .
Poor Greta .
She 's on that list too .
She 's missing all right , but we have no proof she 's dead .
After finding this , what 's the use of hiding from the facts ?
There 's a killer .
A vicious killer .
A girl killer .
We 'll get him .
And when we do ...
Good night , Professor .
Do you know this part of the country ?
No , this is my first trip to Europe .
It 's a very unusual area .
- People call it the Swiss Transylvania . - Why ?
I don 't know . They just do .
So , you are the Corvino girl . Your father is terribly ...
Yes , isn 't he ?
I admire him very much . I thought he might have come with you .
No . Dad 's working in the Philippines .
He 'll be there for almost a year .
He can 't even be reached by telephone .
Well , in any case , he 's placed you in good hands .
I 'm sure you 're going to like our school
To begin with , we all speak English .
And then our academic programme is based on the American one .
Ah ! A bee !
Oh ! Be careful ! It might sting you !
No , leave it alone !
Look out !
No , don 't kill it ! Please !
- Don 't touch it ! - Stop yelling !
- It 's a bee ! - I know .
It won 't hurt me . Insects never hurt me .
I love them .
- You ... you love them ? - Yes .
I love all insects .
' And so Jennifer arrives in Switzerland from the New World
' to pass her first memorable night
' at the Richard Wagner International School for girls.â  
Take the bags in , please .
Impressive , isn 't it ?
The estate was once Richard Wagner 's home .
The school only occupies the main building .
The others are closed because they 're not safe .
Never go into them , ever .
Come along .
I 'm starved . Is there anything to eat ?
No , sorry .
Because of the time changes ,
I haven 't eaten anything but breakfast for two days .
- What are they ? - Baby food .
My parents left it ,
when they came to visit me with my little brother .
Chicken , beef
mixed vegetables .
He 's seven months old .
I bet he 's the only male
who 's ever seen me inside of this place .
Mixed vegetables , great . I 'm a vegetarian .
- I ... I need a ... - Spoon ? No .
Ah .
- How is it ? - Like cat food .
By the way , I 'm Sophie . I 'm French .
- Jennifer . - Hi .
Have you met the headmistress yet ?
Speaking of the devil .
You are the new girl . You were expected this afternoon .
My plane was late because of bad weather .
Would you like some ?
The school has its rules .
I 'm sorry , but I must confiscate this .
Hey , wait . You don 't know who that is . That 's Paul Corvino !
Sophie , that 's enough . Get into bed .
And if I catch you smoking again , you will be sorry .
And you , young lady , to bed .
And switch off the light .
That bitch , stealing Paul Corvino .
Yeah , it 's all right . I have a bunch of them in my bag .
So , tomorrow , I 'll put them all up all over the room .
I 've seen all his movies . I saw his last one three times .
Lucky you .
He must have made me sit through it at least 15 times .
He says he trusts my opinion .
- You mean you know him ? - Yes , of course I do .
Have you been to bed with him ?
Paul Corvino is my father .
- Sorry . - It 's all right .
Your mother lives in India and owns a hotel ?
- She remarried . - Your father never did .
You were only seven when they split up .
- No , I was eight . - Eight ! You were seven .
How do you know so much about Paul Corvino ?
- I read " Cine Review " . - Oh .
Well , it was Christmas Day
and we were opening presents together
and the phone rang .
So , Mom answered it
and she said
" I 'll be right there ! "
And it was her lover .
So , then she left
and she never came back .
But I remember that Dad got 12 presents that year
and he said the 13th was Mom walking out on him like that .
You didn 't read that in " Cine Review " , did you ?
You know , I 'm really glad you 're here .
I 've always had to sleep alone .
It can be very scary . Thanks for coming .
I 'm the one who should thank you .
Don 't let me forget , I owe you a meal .
You know , there 's a murderer around here . A crazy man .
A maniac who kidnaps girls our age and kills them .
And then he hides the bodies .
Can we change the subject ? I need my sleep .
I 'm really tired from the trip .
You 're right .
Sometimes I lie awake all night , thinking about it .
What do you think about before you fall asleep ?
My father .
If I thought about your father , I 'd never get any sleep .
You mind if I watch TV ? I 've got earphones .
No problem . Good night , Sophie .
Good night , Jennifer .
Jâ   As a young boy chasing dragons with your wooden sword so mighty
Jâ   You 're St George or you 're David
Jâ   And you always kill the beast
Jâ   Times change very quickly and you had to grow up early
Jâ   A house in smoking ruins and the bodies at your feet
Jâ   You 'll die as you lived in a flash of the blade
Jâ   In a corner forgot by no one
Jâ   You lived for the touch for the feel of the steel
Jâ   One man and his honour ... Jâ  
- Shit ! - Are you OK ?
Are you foreign ? Are you hurt ?
Let me go .
- Let me go . No . No . - Come on .
- In you get . - No . No .
No . No !
Why are you dressed like that ?
Do you understand me ?
- Hey , do you understand me ? - I 'm sleepwalking .
The last devil .
Maybe she 's on drugs . Open your eyes .
I need to wake up .
Let me go !
Cut it out ! Sit still , you little shit !
- Where did she go ? - I can 't see anything .
Gosh ! She 's gone !
Come on , let 's go .
Is this the first time you 've been sleepwalking ?
No , it 's happened before in the States .
You look a mess , child . Have you any idea where you 've been ?
No . It 's all a blank .
I never remember anything .
- My saviour . - So , you 're American ?
Mm-hm . I 'm studying at the academy .
- Where are you from ? - I 'm from Scotland .
I came here as a student and stayed to teach .
Then I had this accident and I haven 't moved since .
- What do you teach ? - Entomology . I study insects .
Really ?
- Do insects interest you ? - Yeah , a lot . I love them .
- Do you mean that ? - Absolutely . Why ?
You remind me of another girl .
Greta . She used to come here sometimes , help out .
Mostly secretarial work and then ...
Then ?
She was supposed to come here one night . She never arrived .
- The killer got her . - What do you know about that ?
Well , you used the past tense , as if she were dead .
She left her coat here .
You must be frozen , child .
It should fit you . It 's upstairs .
Here , she 'll show you where it is .
No , wait a second . Wait a second .
What are you doing ?
Nice , I like it .
There 's a good boy .
Now , don 't play any tricks .
Bull 's-eye !
What beats me is that it never misses .
The species is supposed to be practically blind .
Thanks . Be careful . You 're in range .
It won 't do anything to me .
You look like Greta in that coat .
She liked insects too .
But they didn 't like her the way that one likes you .
That sound that you can hear is a mating call .
You 're exciting it .
Smell it .
- Go on . Go on , smell it . - You sure ?
It 's sort of sweet .
That substance is secreted by a gland .
It too is meant to attract a mate .
You 're exciting him , and he 's doing his best to excite you .
And to think we only just met .
This isn 't the mating season . I can 't understand it .
I 've never seen anything like it before .
Well , thanks for everything .
Stop by any time .
Good night .
You make an old man happy . Take the cable car .
It 's only a five-minute ride from the town .
I don 't know . Maybe .
And mind how you go with that sleepwalking .
If it happens to you again , you must say , " I am sleepwalking .
" I must wake up .
" I am sleepwalking . I must wake up . "
I 'm sleepwalking . I must wake up .
I 'm sleepwalking .
I won 't need it . I haven 't had an attack for ages .
It must have been the trip out .
Or maybe the change of air .
Maybe the wind .
The wind ? Yes .
The FÃ ¶ hn . A very particular wind .
Typical of this part of the country .
It comes from the Alps .
The blasts of warm air cause snow avalanches .
Make the flowers grow .
The hatching of the larvae .
Some people get headaches .
When it blows , there are those who say it causes madness .
It 's a strange part of the country .
The Swiss Transylvania .
what this E.E.G. is supposed to do ?
What you did last night is highly irregular .
No student ever left the school at night before .
How many times do I have to tell you
that I didn 't walk out on purpose ?
I walk in my sleep .
It happens .
But it is not normal . It 's our duty to know more .
But I know everything there is to know about it .
But this could be leading up to something far more serious .
You say you remember nothing .
This is not a matter of talking in your sleep
or ransacking the fridge .
It could be leading up to a new personality trying to emerge .
Sometimes it 's the first step on the path to schizophrenia .
So , you think I 'm crazy , huh ? Well , you can forget your E.E.G.
There now . Calm down , calm down .
OK , OK , go ahead .
I 'll show you which one of us is crazy .
- What happened ? - That 's strange .
Do you suffer from epilepsy ?
Or do you take something like ... do you understand , drugs ?
I am not crazy , schizophrenic , epileptic or stoned .
Sophie , I need to speak to you , remember ?
Please , Sophie . I need to tell you something .
Hello ? Shapiro Evans ?
Hi . I 'd like to speak to Morris , please .
I mean Mr Shapiro . Jennifer Corvino .
Right , Paul Corvino 's daughter .
He 's out of town ?
Three days ?
What do you mean , it 's a holiday ? What holiday is it ?
Passover ?
Hey , look who 's there .
Zombie .
Hey , have you heard ? She walks in her sleep .
Walks in her sleep ? If you ask me , she 's got problems .
So , that 's Paul Corvino 's daughter .
That still doesn 't give her the right to be such a show-off .
Here she comes .
- What 's wrong ? - Damn Morris .
- Who 's he ? Your boyfriend ? - No .
He 's my father 's agent and attorney .
I want to tell him to get me out of this shitty school .
- He found it . - Why do you want to leave ?
Your little brother isn 't the only male to have graced this place .
- First , you forgot the doctor . - He 's not a man .
He 's got more hands than the entire basketball team .
And second , you forgot the killer .
Killer .
What is the poet trying to say with these words ?
Well ? Who 's going to answer ? You tell us .
- Me ? - Yes , you , Elizabeth .
I think the poet took the words right out of a Bee Gees song .
That 's very funny .
The poet in question is Abraham Cowley .
What if the killer saw me ?
- I 'm really scared . - I would be too .
Can you imagine if I walk in my sleep again tonight ?
I 'm going to run right into him .
Please , promise you 'll keep an eye on me tonight .
We 'll lock the door .
And if you hear me get up or do anything , wake me .
Promise ?
Please say yes .
- Sophie ? You tell us . - Me ?
Yes . Stand up .
Um ... um ...
The poet , through his oracular style ...
The poet , through his auricular style ...
- Oracular . - ... oracular style
tells us of the dangers we face ,
should we forget the sense and meaning of the past .
... tells us of the danger we face ,
should we forget the sense and the meaning of the past .
And do you believe that danger exists ?
- Screw the past . - Screw the past .
Right on , Sophie .
Silence !
And what about Ancient Greece ? Shakespeare ?
OK , I 'll keep an eye on you tonight .
- And Richard Wagner ! - Richard Gere !
Good evening . We start with some sad news .
- Do you like it ? - Nice ! Where did it come from ?
I put it on by mistake . Guess who it belongs to .
Paul Corvino 's daughter .
- Yeah ? The actor ? - Yes .
Her name is Jennifer and she 's my roommate .
All right !
Oh , yes , he 's fantastic . All those muscles !
Not him , her . What is she like ?
Oh , she 's pretty . She wears her hair like mine .
I have to watch her at night because she walks in her sleep .
- Walks in her sleep ? - Yeah .
She gets up and she walks like this .
Really , Sophie , I have to go .
I have to join my regiment at dawn
and you know it 's nearly a three-hour trip .
Come on , stay a while longer .
I can 't . I really have to go .
You shit !
- What did you say ? - I said fuck you !
I 'm sleepwalking .
I must ...
must ...
I must wake up .
Sophie ?
' The police came this morning .
' My pal the headmistress
' told them not to believe anything I say ,
' because she thinks I 'm crazy .
' Maybe you think I 'm crazy too , Dad ,
' if Production ever gets this letter to you .
' I mean , there was really nothing I could do .
' l was so scared that I couldn 't say anything about what I saw
' or why I screamed.â  
So , you think the glove belonged to the killer ?
Yeah , I 'm sure of it .
But why the maggot ?
They 're larvae .
If you give me time , I 'll identify them .
I 'll be able to give you an answer .
Perhaps to some other questions as well .
You won 't , Professor .
Oh , it 's all right . I know the way .
- Jennifer ! - Mm-hm ?
You 're forgetting your notebooks .
Thanks .
Have you any idea why they behave like that ?
Never done this before .
It 's probably because of me .
I guess they sense the mood I 'm in .
I 'm often in a bad mood , upset about something ,
but they don 't carry on like this .
In Ancient Greece , the butterfly symbolises the soul ,
the so-called psyche .
From the Greek , butterfly , psyche .
What is this association between insects and the human soul ? Huh ?
Is it because of the multifarious mystery of them both ?
And we know something about that , don 't we ?
OK .
You see that glove ?
An insect , a firefly , led me to it .
The police came to the school .
They asked me a lot of questions .
But I didn 't tell them how I found the glove .
I didn 't want them to think I was crazy .
You can tell me . I 'm not the police .
What happened ?
I was standing alone
in the dark .
And ...
I needed help .
And a firefly ... it was like it heard me
and it answered my call .
You 've calmed them down just by telling me that .
But that 's ridiculous .
It 's new .
That 's the essence of discovery to a scientist .
If you only knew the things I 've discovered .
Things my fellow scientists consider absurd .
Extrasensory perception .
The paranormal powers that are unusual in human beings
are perfectly normal in insects .
Some species communicate with each other
over vast distances by telepathy .
These little creatures have enormous power .
I could give you a multitude of examples .
I wrote a book about this very subject . You may have it .
It 's perfectly normal for insects
to be slightly telepathic .
Yeah , it 's normal for insects .
But am I normal ?
Jennifer ! Eurgh !
But why me ?
Fraulein Corvino cannot be left alone .
I want someone in here with her .
And I want to know everything she says and does .
I 'm scared of her . She arrived and Sophie disappeared .
Plus she 's crazy . Listen to this .
" Dear Dad ... "
Ah , here it is . " Do you remember what the doctor said
" about sleepwalking manifesting a split personality ?
" It 's true , my second personality is emerging .
" Do you know how ? I communicate with insects . "
" I mean I 've discovered I have power over them .
" I 'm not kidding , I even have a witness ,
" the famous entomologist John McGregor , who lives near here .
- " We 've become friends ... " - You see ? She is crazy .
This is mine .
- Hey , Jennifer , listen ! - What ?
Bzz .
- I 'm a spider ! - And I 'm a worm .
- Speak and you shall be obeyed . - No , no !
Stop it ! Stop it !
I 'm a killer spray ! Death to all insects !
- I 'm a mosquito ! - I 'm a fly !
- I 'm a mosquito ! A mosquito ! - I 'm a spider ! I 'm a spider !
We worship you ! We worship you !
We worship you ! We worship you ! We worship you !
- Now , that 's enough , girls ! - We worship you !
We worship you ! We worship you !
I love you .
I love you all .
I love all of you .
- She 's still asleep . - I called an ambulance
to have her taken to the mental hospital .
They 'll be here any minute .
At least they 'll be better equipped to keep her calm .
- But is she insane ? - Well , she 's not normal .
- She 's diabolic . - Diabolic ?
Yes . The Bible also refers to the devil as Baalzebub ,
which means Lord of the flies .
Look at her , the Lady of the flies .
Call me as soon as she wakes up .
Mmf .
Ah .
Diabolic ?
Hey , does Jennifer look like a devil to you ? Huh ?
No . You 're not a devil .
The only devil around here is the killer .
But I understand how you must be feeling .
I know what it feels like to be different .
And the conditions that go with it , pity , irony , revulsion ...
annoyance .
People have the ability to make you almost hate yourself .
There 's a big difference between you and me .
When that car bashed into me , I lost something .
But you , you gained something .
You 're in a position to do extraordinary things
with that gift of yours .
Come on ! I want to show you something .
Come on , Inga .
Look , these were inside the glove .
Larvae of the Great Sarcophagus .
A rather menacing name ,
appropriate to the insect that bears it .
It lives exclusively off dead bodies . Human remains .
The Great Sarcophagus .
What a weird name !
They 're a destroyer , a flesh-eater .
It is capable of picking up the scent of a dead body
over vast distances .
Its sensory perception is extraordinary , quite unique .
But why did the glove have so many larvae in it ?
Perhaps because when the murderer hides his victims ,
he likes to keep in physical contact with them .
Conserving them .
He is a psychopath .
If we mean to get him ,
we have to call on the services
of the two greatest detectives ever known .
Perhaps I should say unknown up until now .
Who are they ?
You
and him .
The Great Sarcophagus .
Hold out your hand .
There .
See , he 's not afraid of you . He won 't do that for me .
Ask him to lead you where the dead bodies are hidden ,
and he 'll lead you .
That fly is your magic wand .
You think it 'll work ?
With your gift .
It 'll take a lifetime . It could be anywhere .
Not anywhere .
On a 52-kilometre route .
The first girl to disappear was a Danish tourist .
She took a bus on the Red Line .
It starts on the city square on a 52-kilometre route ,
calling at various tourist traps on the way .
She was seen getting on that bus .
When you get near to the killer 's house ,
you 'll know about it soon enough ,
because the Sarcophagus will go crazy
and head straight for the dead bodies .
All you have to do is follow it and come straight back .
Do you feel up to it ?
Yeah .
I want him caught .
For Sophie .
She was my friend .
And I want him caught for Greta .
I wish you all the luck in the world .
My two detectives .
Excuse me , Miss .
Excuse me , Miss !
- I don 't understand German . - Please close the window .
- The wind ! - No !
So badly behaved !
Wait ! Wait ! Please !
Thanks .
- What are you doing here ? - I was following a ...
Who are you ? You came here to steal , did you ?
No ! I was looking for someone !
You were looking for someone ? Come on , the house is empty .
No-one 's lived here
since the former tenants moved out eight months ago .
The house is for sale !
- I 'm really sorry ! - Sure !
I didn 't mean to cause any harm !
- Ugh ! - Hey !
Ah .
May I help you ?
- Who are you ? - I 'm the estate agent .
If you 're looking for a house , I 'm your man .
Uh-huh . Anyone living in the house now ?
No . By the way , where did you come from ?
- I didn 't hear you drive up . - I came from the back .
How long has the house been empty ?
I don 't know . Seven , eight months maybe .
Who was living here before ?
I would have to check at the agency .
But we do not give out that kind of information .
It 's absolutely confidential and against our company ...
I 'm Inspector Geiger . Cantonal Police .
It 's all right , Inga .
You 've locked yourself out , you silly girl .
This damn machine !
What on earth is going on round here ?
Who 's that ? Is there someone there ?
Wait !
Who is it ?
Hey !
Answer me !
Who are you ?
Aaah !
Jâ   You know I 'm rollin ' , know I 'm coming through
Jâ   Hear me howlin ' , catchin ' up on you
Jâ   Check on your time ' cause I ain 't never coming back
Jâ   You know I 'm loaded
Jâ   Railroaded
Jâ   I 'm explosive
Jâ   I 'm a locomotive ... Jâ  
Most of our patients are kept under restraint .
Take my word for it , Inspector .
The person you 're looking for is not one of ours .
No-one 's ever escaped from here .
Correct . But I 'm working from the exact opposite assumption .
How can I explain ?
It isn 't as if someone got out of your institution
but rather got in .
You have had such a case , I believe ?
Yes , a curious incident .
It happened about 15 years ago
here on the lower basement level .
Since then , it 's only been accessible
to members of the staff .
The further down one goes in this place ,
the more monstrous the inmates become .
It 's probably the same in hell .
Until you reach the last circle , the one without a centre .
Shit , Morris ! I 'm telling you ,
I won 't stay here a minute longer .
I want to come home and I don 't have the money for a ticket .
No , I ran away from school .
' Cause they wanted to lock me in an institution !
What ?
It 's a long story .
Get me back to LA . and I 'll tell you all about it .
Which bank do you use in Zurich ?
The S.K.A ? What does it stand for ?
Hello .
Send me some money . A telex in my name .
Do it , Morris !
I don 't want to be murdered .
Yes , I said murder .
Someone here wants to kill me and he 's tried once already .
I 'm sorry . There 's nothing here in your name .
- Are you sure ? - I 'm afraid so .
Maybe it just arrived
and it hasn 't come through the computers yet .
I can check .
There 's nothing . I 'm sorry .
Now what am I supposed to do ? This is an emergency .
It could arrive at any time .
Look , why don 't you come back later ?
Where can I go in the meantime ? Can I wait here ?
Sure , you can wait over there .
But I suggest you go for a walk .
I 'll wait .
Hello , Jennifer .
Your father 's attorney Mr Shapiro called us from New York .
He was very worried about you .
And extremely angry with us for , let 's say , losing you .
What a bastard .
He sounded very reasonable on the phone .
He spoke to me and only calmed down
when I told him I would come for you myself .
He said I would find you here .
I 'm not going back to that school .
Of course not .
He said you want to go back to America immediately .
- Is that true ? - Yes .
Well , he authorised me to buy your ticket
and give you some money .
Is that all right ?
- OK . - Good .
Good luck !
- What time is my flight ? - 12 noon tomorrow .
The last flight out today has already left .
What about tonight ? I 'm not going to sleep at the school .
I 'm not going back there . I 'm not gonna sleep there .
I never want to see the place again .
Don 't worry . If that 's what you want , it 's all right .
Mr Shapiro said to do whatever you wanted .
You can stay with me tonight .
It 's enormous . Do you live here alone ?
No .
You 'll sleep in here , Jennifer .
I hope you find it comfortable enough .
Looks fine . Thank you .
Why are the mirrors covered like that ?
I told you , I don 't live alone . I have a small son .
He 's very sick .
I cover the mirrors for his sake .
He doesn 't want to see his reflection .
I worry about him very much . He 's changed my life completely .
Sometimes I think he 's driving me crazy .
- I 'm sorry . - Oh .
These are things that can happen in a woman 's life .
But don 't worry . You won 't see him .
- Oh , I don 't mind if ... - No . It 's better if you don 't .
He stays in his room with his crazy thoughts .
Would you like something ? A cup of tea ?
No , I don 't want to bother you .
It 's no bother .
I 'm sorry . I kicked the train by mistake .
It hit him .
- Maybe he 's hurt . - Hurt ?
- Don 't grab him like that ! - Why not ?
What on earth are you thinking ?
This is my son ?
It 's only a doll .
You 're a very sensitive young lady . Are you frightened ?
- No , no . - Yes , you are .
I can see it in your eyes .
You 're burning up .
- You have a fever . - No , I don 't .
Yes , you do .
In this part of the country , with this wind ,
it 's hardly surprising .
I 'll get you a pill .
You don 't want to leave with a cold tomorrow , do you ?
Imagine what Mr Shapiro would say .
You should take them both . But if you prefer , one is enough .
I don 't want any pills .
- May I use the bathroom ? - The bathroom is over there .
And you will take the pills .
I never take medicine .
Do as you 're told . You 're my responsibility .
Listen , there 's nothing wrong with me .
- What kind of tablets are they ? - They 'll stop your fever .
They won 't do you any harm , that 's for sure .
I 'm in charge of you
and if I tell you to take them , you have to take them .
You 're hurting me . Let me go .
Take them !
All right , I 'll take the pills .
- I 'll get you some water . - I can get it myself .
Shit , get out of the way !
May I close the door ?
What a bitch .
' Larvae of the Great Sarcophagus .
' It lives exclusively off dead bodies , human remains.â  
Poison !
Jennifer , what are you doing ?
- Poison ! - Jennifer , answer me !
Open the door !
I said what are you doing ?
Answer me , Jennifer ! Open the door this instant !
Open the door !
Answer me ! How dare you behave like this ?
Jennifer !
Let me in !
Why didn 't you open the door ? What were you doing ?
Did you take the pill ? What were you doing ?
Who are you calling ?
Morris . I want to tell him everything 's fine .
- Tomorrow . - No , I want to do it now .
- Just a few seconds . - No !
Let go of me !
I said no ! You mustn 't call anybody , do you understand ?
You 're in my house and you will do what I say !
Help ! Help !
Stay there . If you say a word , I 'll kill you !
15 years ago , when you were still working in Basel
you were assaulted .
Surely you haven 't forgotten the incident ?
No . Look at this .
Oh ! He pulled me to him through the bars .
There were bars between us .
I understand , Frau Brückner . Forgive me .
But we have to be precise .
So , you moved here eight months ago . Is that correct ?
Yes , that is so , Inspector . Please come this way .
And where were you living before that ?
Outside Zurich .
Oh .
' Perhaps the murderer hides his victims .
' He likes to keep in physical contact with them ,
' conserving them .
' He 's a psychopath.â  
Jâ   As a young boy chasing dragons with your wooden sword so mighty
Jâ   You 're St George or you 're David
Jâ   And you always killed the beast
Jâ   Times change very quickly and you had to grow up early
Jâ   A house in smoking ruins and the bodies at your feet
Jâ   You 'll die as you lived in a flash of the blade
Jâ   In a corner forgot by no one
Jâ   You live for the touch For the feel of the steel
Jâ   One man and his honour
Jâ   The smell of resined leather
Jâ   The steely iron mask
Jâ   As you cut and thrust and parried
Jâ   At the fencing master 's call
Jâ   He taught you all he ever knew
Jâ   To fear no mortal man
Jâ   And now you 'll wreak your vengeance
Jâ   In the screams of evil men
Jâ   You 'll die as you lived ... Jâ  
Jâ   In a corner forgot by no one
Jâ   You lived for the touch , for the feel of the steel
Jâ   One man and his honour ... Jâ  
- Mr Shapiro ? - Yes .
The car rental agency . Your car is right outside .
Here 's the key . Do you need a map , sir ?
No , thank you . I know the area .
Jennifer !
Hello ?
Don 't be afraid .
I 'm Inspector Geiger . I 've come to help you !
Help me !
Thank you .
You fucking bitch !
You bitch !
I 'll get you !
Go away ! You scare me !
- I won 't hurt you . - I don 't want you here !
I know your mother was bad .
But I want to help .
You don 't have to worry about the mirrors anymore .
It 's all over .
No ! Please ! No ! Please !
No ! No ! No !
- Morris ! - Jennifer ?
- Morris ! - Thank God !
Aaah ! Aaah !
He was diseased ...
but he was my son .
And you have ...
Why didn 't I kill you before ?
I killed that ... that inspector and your professor friend ,
to protect him ,
and now I 'm going to kill you ,
to avenge him !
Why don 't you call your insects ?
Go on !
Call ! Call !